https://www.deifratelli.com/dei-fratelli-privacy-policy/

Dei Fratelli Privacy Policy
Dei Fratelli (Hirzel Canning Company) understands that many visitors to our website are concerned about how their personal information they provide online is used and maintained by Dei Fratelli. This privacy policy has been created to address these concerns and to demonstrate how we gather, and provide, information. Our privacy policy may be updated from time to time, so please check back occasionally.
Gathering and Use Of Information
DeiFratelli.com may collect personally identifiable information from visitors on a voluntary basis when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, or enter information on our site. Personal information may include your name, postal address, e-mail address, and/or telephone numbers, etc. We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer any personal information we gather on our website to any third parties without your prior consent. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Personal information is collected for the following reasons: 1) to e-mail consumers via our On The Vine eNewsletter, 2) to notify winners of contests and to distribute prizes, 3) to distribute items that are part of “giveaways” that you have registered for, 4) for use in our online and off-line marketing and advertising campaigns. 5) To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
Contests/Sweepstakes
We occasionally run contests on our website for which we ask participants to provide contact information. This information is used to contact the participant only when necessary in accordance with the rules of the contest or sweepstakes.
Cookies
Dei Fratelli may use cookies to track customer visits through our sites. Cookies are small files of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) for record-keeping purposes. This enhances your experience by saving your preferences while visiting a specific site.
We use cookies to understand and save user’s preferences for future visits and to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your online experience more efficient may not function properly; however, your experience on DeiFratelli.com should not change.
We do not use cookies that contain any personally identifying information and cannot profile your system or collect information from your hard drive.
Polls & Surveys
Dei Fratelli may gather information from polls and/or surveys. This information is for internal use only. Any answers to polls or surveys are posted, there will be no identifiable personal information included.
Opt-Out
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from all On The Vine eNewsletter correspondence.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email, phone, or mail.
Hirzel Canning Company
Attn: Customer Service Department
411 Lemoyne Rd.
Request Product From Grocer (PDF)
